Dominic J Mitchell

1-401-440-3243

dominic.joseph.mitchell.2018@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/dominic-j-mitchell https://github.com/DominicJosephMitchell

Energetic & dynamic Full Stack Web Developer, Specializing in Front End Web Design. A business professional enthusiastic about Tech while constantly learning, and stretching the borders of my mind. I decided to continue my education to increase and advance my Tech knowledge and career. Graduate of (IEL) Institute – of – Entrepreneurship & Leadership, and Rhode Coders Web Development, and currently enrolled in (GA) General Assembly. With 30 years experience in Management, Leadership, Construction & eight years Technology skills.

Employment History

| Web Design & Developer Fellow | GA – General Assembly | 10/2018-01/2019 |
|--|---|-----------------|
| *Twelve week web development immersiv | | |
| Advanced Support Center Eng I | Cox Communications | 01/2013-06/2018 |
| *Team Lead&Trainer. Tester New Deployn | | |
| App Specialist – III Lead/Trainer | Up-Source | 01/2012-12/2012 |
| *Level III Lead & Rep Trainer | | _ |
| Consultant/Tech- Tier I, II | TMC | 11/2010-01/2012 |
| *Establish/Direct/ Increase Profit Yearly. | | |
| Founder / Entrepreneur | Mitchell Construction Inc | 04/2004-11/2010 |
| *Risk bearing, organizing, and innovation. | _Planning, organizing, leading, and controlling | |

Education

| Institute – of – Entrepreneurship & Leadership | | |
|--|--|------|
| *HTML – CSS – JavaScript | Web Design & Deployment | |
| New Horizons Computer Learning Center | | |
| *A+, Net+, Sec+, MCP&MCDST | Network Support Technician Certificate | |
| Community College of Rhode Island | | 2003 |
| *Associates in Arts Degree | | |

Scrum/Agile

Wire-frame

Ruby Node.JS

API

_

Technical Skills

React

| | CILLED | | | | |
|---------|--------|------------|------------|---------|---------------|
| HMTL | CSS | JavaScript | Handlebars | Ajax | Ruby-on-Rails |
| MongoDB | SOL | PM/BA | Leadership | Git-Hub | Management |

Mongoose Networking

Web Development Projects

Bash

- * **Tic-Tac-Toe:** A custom front-end JavaScript game engine which connects with a third-party API. Users sign-up/in with an email address to create an account.
- * Vacations: HTML and CSS multi-page user experience designed photo album.
- * Family Tree: HTML, CSS, and JavaScript ancestry database; users can sign-up/in with an email to create account.